Nathanael Gazzard

2 Cataract Street, Kaleen, ACT 2617 0472 602 363 nathanael.gazzard@gmail.com

As a result of the broad range of roles I have worked in, I am quick to adapt to new environments, form positive relationships with colleagues and clients alike, and rapidly learn and master new tools, skills, and systems. I have extensive customer service experience in retail and in providing technical services to clients in sensitive situations. I am adept at working autonomously, managing my time and priorities to ensure that I always fulfil my duties to a high standard by their respective deadlines. I am an amicable individual who enjoys working as a part of a team and continually strives to contribute my best work.

Professional Skills:

Records Management
Customer Service
Effective Written and Verbal Communication
Event Planning and Coordination
Developing Standard Operating Procedures
Producing Training Material
Team Leadership
Email Announcements and Updates
Performing Under Pressure
Time & Priority Management

Technical Skills/Qualifications:

Bachelor of IT (in progress)
Certificate III in IT
Diploma of Design
Baseline Security Clearance (former)
First Aid Certificate
C#, JS, HTML, CSS, Python, SQLite
Database systems (CASA RMS, DDS MMS)
MS Office Suite
Photoshop CS6
Blender 3D Modelling Software

Employment History:

Pharmacy Assistant at Kaleen Discount Drug Stores

09/2021 – 08/2023. 3 Gwydir Square, Kaleen ACT 2617 (resigned to study full-time)

Duties: Implementing and maintaining an administrative system to track requesting dates for schedule-8 medication scripts. Filing and administration. Records management and disposal. Pharmacy dispensing. Answering customer phone enquiries. Making corrections to Webster-packed medications.

In this role: I developed and implemented a system for reliably tracking which scripts our aged-care patients currently have and when it is necessary to contact their doctors for new ones, ensuring we always have the schedule-8 scripts required for their daily delivery. I work flexibly, undertaking any tasks that will facilitate the pharmacists to do their work unimpeded.

Referee: Roda Elzahaby, Pharmacist & Owner (supervisor) Contact: 0478 712 785.

Record Management Support Officer at Civil Aviation Safety Authority (CASA)

03/2020 - 06/2021. 26 Furzer St, Aviation House, Phillip ACT 2606.

Duties: Liaising with managers across the organisation for the review and destruction of records in accordance with National Archives Australia (NAA) directives. Facilitating security updates to the records management system. Producing organisation-wide reports on record creation. Producing training material and SOPs for duties performed. Assisting with the delivery of files recalled by staff. Designing and implementing practices to improve the quality of CASA's management of records.

In this role: I consistently processed large quantities of data in short timeframes, whilst maintaining strict data quality to ensure that CASA was compliant with the legal standards required by the NAA. As requirements from the NAA changed and expectations from executive managers shifted, I adapted my working processes to meet those moving goals. I also identified larger challenges facing the Information Management team, then devised and implemented new practices to effectively address the issues, which improved the reliability and effectiveness of the Information Management team overall. I was also one of the first volunteers in a newly created LGBTQIA+ support network, assisting in planning and running events to support diversity and de-stigmatization in the workplace.

Referee: Michelle Massey, Branch Manager (supervisor) Contact: 0434 664 476.

Client Service Centre Officer in Aviation Medicine at CASA

03/2020 - 06/2021. 26 Furzer St, Aviation House, Phillip ACT 2606.

Duties: Assessing pilot medical applications against provided criteria. Answering client phone and email inquiries. Appending forms and medical records to pilot files in the CASA database, adhering to strict data quality guidelines.

In this role: I sought to ensure that each client I interacted with left satisfied with the service they received, working hard to reassure and assist clients who were distressed in relation to their applications. In the rare instances where a suitable resolution could not be reached, I followed the directives provided for escalation. I strove continually to meet the target rate of application processing whilst maintaining the precision needed to achieve CASA's mission of safe skies for all.

Referee: Nathan Sullivan, Section Manager (supervisor) Contact: 6217 1291.

Wait Staff at Bittersweet Cafe

02/2019 - 09/2019. 27 Eyre Street, Cusack Centre, Kingston ACT, 2604.

Referee: Daniel Rayner, Former Owner (supervisor) Contact: 0411 041 951.

Team Member at Coles Gungahlin

10/2015 - 02/2019. Gungahlin Place, Gungahlin ACT, 2912.

Education History:

Bachelor in IT

Griffith University. 2021 - Present (in progress)

Bachelor of Arts in Architecture

University of Canberra. 2014 – 2016 (discontinued)

Diploma of Design

University of Canberra. 2013 – 2014 (graduated)

Certificate III in IT

Unity College. 2012 (graduated)

Volunteer History:

Youth Leader at Gungahlin Youth Group

02/2014 - 02/2021. 104 The Valley Avenue, Gungahlin ACT, 2912.

Duties: Running the organisation (01/2020 - 04/2020). Chairing meetings. Coordinating with other youth organisations and businesses to plan events. Planning and running weekly events. Organizing and leading youth band rehearsals/performances. Composing and delivering weekly email newsletters. Meeting with and supporting leaders under my authority to ensure their well-being. Mentoring youth members.

In this role: I strove to be a positive influence in the lives of the youth I worked with and to exemplify the inclusive values of the Gungahlin Youth Group. I continuously worked to build strong relationships with my fellow leaders. I maintained clear ethical boundaries to ensure the safety of the youth. I chose to leave the organization when a new church took charge of the youth group and required volunteers to formally oppose LGBTQIA+ rights.

Referee: Peter Hocking, Pastor of Cornerstone Christian Church (oversight). Contact: 0494 839 368.

Independent Projects:

I spend what time I can outside of my responsibilities creating video games for both mobile and PC. I use the Unity Game Engine, programming in C#, along with a plethora of software for creating, 2D, 3D, and audio assets. Additionally, I create video game assets to sell on the Unity Asset Store. See my currently published work linked below:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.AnnNateStudios.FruitJuicer

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.AnnNateStudios.TwoStepsBack

https://late-night-game-studio.itch.io/nates-horror-anthology-volume-1

https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/3d/characters/antique-suitcases-briefcases-chests-113708

https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/3d/characters/antique-lounge-set-102305

https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/3d/props/wooden-shipping-crates-97877